Amy Neugent

Staff Pharmacist - Virtua-West Jersey Health System

Maple Shade, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Amy-Neugent/24672123cfe1df9e

I am a licensed Pharmacist with 23 years of hospital pharmacy experience, committed to providing quality pharmaceutical care as an essential link in disease management.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Staff Pharmacist

Virtua-West Jersey Health System - August 1992 to Present

multiple divisions

Demonstrated versatility in working at various divisions, in several different shifts. Promoting safe and effective age-specific drug therapy by reviewing and evaluating physician orders. Responsibilities include: providing drug information; following established and policies and procedures; adhering to state, federal regulations and JCAHO standards, clarifying orders; educating associates, patients and families; performing clinical functions; therapeutic substitutions; supervising ancillary pharmacy associates; ensures the provision of processes to optimize pharmaceutical care, including minimizing the risk of adverse events and medication errors. Duties also include utilizing CPOE to ensure all orders are correct and justified, troubleshooting problems with Pyxis machines, insuring that all medications leaving the department are correct. Thorough knowledge of all aspects of IV clean room requirements and IV sterile products preparation.

Staff Pharmacist

Virtua-West Jersey Health System - Camden, NJ - March 2007 to April 2014

Experienced in providing all aspects of pharmaceutical care in pediatrics, neonates, ob/gyn, geriatrics, transplant, dialysis, cancer and cardiothoracic surgical patients. Promoting safe and effective age-specific drug therapy by reviewing and evaluating physician orders. Responsibilities include: providing drug information; following established and policies and procedures; adhering to state, federal regulations and pertinent accrediting bodies;

clarifying orders; educating associates, patients and families; performing clinical functions; therapeutic substitutions; supervising ancillary pharmacy associates; ensures the provision of processes to optimize pharmaceutical care, including minimizing the risk of adverse events and medication errors.

Pharmacy Technician

Virtua-West Jersey Health System - Marlton, NJ - September 1987 to August 1992

Duties Included: unit-dose, medication cart filling, and delivery of medication to nursing units, IV admixture, filling of department orders.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Pharmacy

Temple University School of Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA 1992

CERTIFICATIONS

NJ licensed pharmacist

April 2017

CPR Certification

July 2017